[grave music]
[breath trembling]
Let us go--
[gasps]
Wait, please don't shoot.
I have a sick daughter at home who…
[groans]
[No-eul] Close your eyes.
If you want to live, do as I say.
[scanner beeps]
[woman on PA] Player 246, eliminated.
SQUID GAME 3
EPISODE 1
KEYS AND KNIVES
[masked soldier] Take him away.
What's with you playing nice with us
all of a sudden?
It's not like you.
[No-eul] I gave it some more thought.
If they're just gonna die anyway,
might as well give their organs
to people who can still be saved.
[masked soldier chuckles]
Good call.
I'm glad to hear you finally came around.
[No-eul] I wanna see it.
-[masked soldier] See what?
-The operating room.
[masked soldier] What for?
[No-eul] Well, now that we're partners,
there shouldn't be any secrets between us.
[alarm buzzing]
[eerie music]
[players whispering indistinctly]
[door closes]
[man 1] Guess it's someone
who died out there.
[man 2] Who is that?
[gasps]
Is he dead?
He's alive.
-Come here. Help me get him to a bed.
-[sighs]
-Quick!
-[Yong-sik] Yeah, of course.
[Geum-ja] Here, just…
Wait, lay him down here.
[mercenary] I don't see him
anywhere near the boat.
Do you remember how many drinks he had?
Not enough to get wasted.
Sure looked like a lot
from those soju bottles
on the cabin floor this morning.
He could've gotten drunk,
came out to the deck to throw up,
and ended up falling overboard.
The waves were pretty rough last night.
Oh, you know,
I wonder if that was the sound I heard.
What sound?
Uh, at some point,
someone was talking outside,
then I heard these thumping sounds.
What time was that?
I think it was about 3:00 a.m. Wasn't it?
Yep, that sounds about right.
I got up to check, but Captain Park
was already out on the deck.
[groans] We should've woken everyone up
and looked for him.
We should search the vicinity first.
Listen, Detective,
these are strong currents we got out here.
He would've drifted quite a ways
since last night.
If he was drunk when he fell,
in weather like that, well…
Can you waste time
looking for a corpse? Huh?
You said we had three, four days, at most.
We'll head to the nearest docks
and find another drone pilot.
Let's move out.
[ominous music]
[In-ho] We have to attack first.
[Gi-hun] Doesn't mean we should join
this bloodbath.
We'd be playing into their hands
if we did.
[In-ho] Sacrifice a few for the rest?
[Gi-hun] And it'll be worth the sacrifice
if it means we can put an end
to these games for good.
[Jung-bae] If they won't let us go
we fight our way out.
[Gi-hun] If you wanna take out
these fuckers, step forward.
[Jung-bae]
Why take me instead of Young-il?
[Gi-hun] 'Cause you're my best friend.
[Geum-ja shakily] Mr. Seong.
[tense music]
Oh, you… Oh, goodness, you're awake.
You're alive.
[laughing] You're alive.
Are you feeling better, sir?
[players murmuring]
[man] It's suspicious, right?
[murmuring continues]
Where's… where's everyone else?
And Jung-bae, did he…
[sinister music]
[Front Man] Now, witness the consequences
of your little game.
[Jung-bae] Gi-hun…
[gunshot]
[dark music]
[breath trembling]
[alarm buzzing]
-[door closes]
-[remote beeps]
[ceiling rumbles]
[digital trilling]
[masked manager] Last night,
another 35 players were eliminated,
bringing the current number
of remaining players to 60.
The total prize is now 39.6 billion won,
and each player's share
is 660 million won.
We will now begin another round of voting
to determine if you wish to proceed
to the next game.
[footsteps approaching]
Why'd you let me live, and no one else?
Why didn't you kill me?
Answer me!
What's it for, huh?
You didn't let anyone else live. Why?!
Here, go ahead.
Shoot. Go ahead, pull the trigger!
Go on, do it!
Kill me. Take the shot!
Why did you let me live? Why?
What else do you bastards want from me?
Why didn't you just kill me
like everyone else?
[sobbing]
You won, didn't you?
Go ahead, just take the fucking shot!
You beat us! You won!
-So please, I'm begging you, just kill me!
-[phone ringing]
[screams] Kill me!
We just docked at the nearest port.
They're gonna find another drone pilot
and head out again.
They must not find the island.
Not till we're done
with all the games here.
[Captain] Understood.
Hey, Detective Hwang!
Gimme a call
once you're ready to head back out!
-Will do.
-[Captain] And, uh, watch your step there.
Last question.
What do I do if things go south?
Kill them all.
Including the detective.
[somber music]
[masked manager]
We will now begin another round of voting
to determine if you wish to proceed
to the next game.
Once again, it will be conducted
in reverse player-number order.
Player 456, please cast your vote.
If you do not express an intent to vote
by the count of three,
it will be considered an abstention.
One, two, three.
Player 456 has forfeited his vote,
and as such,
his will not be added to either tally.
Next, Player 448. Please cast your vote.
[man 1] Don't worry, you can relax.
We're not gonna hurt you, okay?
[man 2] Yeah, you can vote for either one!
[man 3]
Don't worry about anyone else, okay?
Just vote however you want!
[beeps]
-[excited whispering]
-[man 4] First one's with us.
[elevator door closes]
[Masked Officer]
So far, the confirmed casualties
are 8 managers and 27 soldiers.
[Front Man] Pull from the workers
to replace the dead soldiers.
And repair any damage to the facility
as quickly as possible.
The VIPs will be arriving soon.
[Masked Officer] Yes, sir.
[ominous music]
[forklift beeping]
[loud thud]
[masked soldier]
Where'd you learn how to shoot?
Oh, wait.
I heard North Korean women have to serve
in the military too. You learn there?
[No-eul] That's right.
[masked soldier]
So then why'd you cross the border?
Were things pretty bad up there?
Or maybe
you landed yourself in some hot water.
[masked soldier sighs]
You said we were partners now.
So shouldn't we get to know
each other a bit?
[No-eul] We can meet on the outside
once this is all over.
I'll tell you everything then.
[masked soldier sighs]
I don't wanna wait till then.
You know,
there's a great place for a date nearby.
Wanna check it out?
[No-eul] It's a long story.
Let me see the operating room first.
[masked soldier] Sure.
I've had my eye on this spot for a while.
You're gonna love it.
[laughs]
[masked manager]
In accordance with the results
of your free and democratic vote,
we will proceed
with the next game tomorrow.
Thank you all.
-[alarm buzzing]
-[door opens]
[indistinct conversations]
[door closes]
[Jeong-dae] Hey, 456.
Tell me something.
Was this part of your plan the whole time?
Oh, that's it, isn't it?
You get everyone
to join your little rebellion
so you could get rid of them all at once.
[snaps fingers]
Ah, so that means that earlier…
-[screaming] …"Why didn't I die?!"
-[players laugh]
All that shit was an act.
Wow. Talk about a twisted freak.
I bet you're right.
'Cause after all,
those assholes killed everyone
but decided to spare him.
There's a reason for that, isn't there?
Well, in any case, you brought those
dumbass Xs out there to die,
so now they're out of our way.
You got us a larger share,
and helped us win today's vote.
Thanks for that.
Now, let's show our man some gratitude
with a round of applause!
-[cheering, whooping]
-[man 1] Good job!
[man 2] Couldn't have done it without ya!
[man 3] You've been on our side all along!
[Seon-nyeo] Oh, you poor fool.
What did I tell you?
You're not here of your own volition,
are you?
It was the vengeful souls
hovering over you
that dragged you here.
[eerie music]
Do you hear that?
It's the sound of all your little friends,
screaming into your ears from the dead.
Ah, but cover them all you want.
It won't stop the noise.
You'll only hear them
scream louder each day.
And you…
You're going to continue to hear them
from now until the day that you die.
[laughing]
[Seon-nyeo gasps]
[Player 006] Let her go!
Stop it! Let her go.
[Gi-hun strains]
[Gi-hun grunts]
[Player 006]
Are you all right, Miss Seon-nyeo?
[Seon-nyeo breathing heavily]
[handcuffs rattling]
[ominous music]
How's this one?
We'll be able to get some good stuff.
[eerie music]
[man 1] Okay, nice and easy.
-One, two, three!
-[man 2] Three!
[door opens]
[man 3] It's okay. You guys can relax.
Number 011's on our side now.
Your friend there's in good shape, right?
That was all her.
It's a little present for us.
Why'd you bring her all the way down here?
We're all partners now, okay?
We should get to know each other a little.
The guys here before us
only wound up getting caught
'cause they wanted to keep secrets.
There was no trust.
But we trust each other.
We have no secrets.
That's why we agreed
not to wear our masks in here.
Isn't it?
[man 1 exhales]
[doctor] So you're Number 011.
You know much money we lost
'cause of the shit you pulled out there?
That's enough.
We gotta hurry if we're gonna make it.
Help me here.
[man 3] Hey, come here.
I'll walk you through
the whole thing, okay?
There's your present on the table now.
He's still alive, right, Doc?
Yeah. Just unconscious.
All right then.
Let's all thank Number 011
for the lovely gift.
Time to open it.
[doctor chuckles]
-[groans]
-[tense music]
-Freeze.
-[doctor] What the fuck!
Put the knife down.
-Putting it down!
-What are you doing?
[No-eul] You step back!
-[man 3] I thought you were one of us now.
-[man 1] Goddamn bitch!
[man 3 screams]
Fuck.
[breath trembling]
-[gunshot]
-[man 3 gasps]
[breath trembles]
You wanted to know
why I crossed the border?
I had a commander a lot like you up there.
I shot him in the head.
-[chuckles]
-[ominous music]
[breathing heavily] Don't kill me.
I swear, I'm not one of them.
I just got roped into this.
They… they offered me money.
[No-eul] This man…
Save him.
If he dies, so do you.
[mysterious music]
[Myung-gi] Jun-hee.
I know they're your favorite.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'll be fine. You just eat yours.
Um, excuse me, sir.
Here, have this. You need to try and eat.
Listen, I know.
You wanted to help us.
You were trying to save
everyone out there.
To teach those bad people a lesson
and end this whole thing.
I'm sorry.
[dark music]
I should've done more…
to bring the ammo back to you.
Hyun-ju, why are you sorry?
This is Dae-ho's fault.
Come on, I saw it, my mom saw it.
Everyone here saw what happened.
As soon as Dae-ho got here,
he took the rounds,
went to leave, and then just
froze and sank right to the floor.
And by the time Hyun-ju got here,
it was already too late.
The guards had all started to rush in.
And if my mom hadn't stopped her,
then, well,
Hyun-ju would've died too.
That's the truth, right?
[Geum-ja] Look, sitting here
won't bring anyone back from the dead.
Let's focus on who's still here.
Right, sir?
Go on. Try to eat a little.
And please drink some water
so you don't choke.
Oh, dear. He's completely out of it.
[eerie music]
NOVEMBER 4 - DAY 4 OF THE SEARCH
[knocking on door]
[Woo-seok] Detective Hwang, you asleep?
Not yet, no.
Listen, uh, if you're still awake,
I thought we could have a chat
over some drinks.
Sure. Come in.
Thanks.
Oh, no. None for me.
Uh… Okay.
[Woo-seok exhales]
So, what is it? What's on your mind?
Oh.
It's, um, about Captain Park.
You were saying that
when you almost drowned,
-he's who found you at sea?
-[Jun-ho] Yeah.
I fell into the water
after I got shot on that island.
He's the one who rescued me
and then took me to the hospital.
Well, is there anything else you remember?
No. I woke up in the hospital room.
My mother's the one who told me
what he did.
Why?
Uh… [laughs awkwardly]
Uh, it's nothing, just…
Do you remember this morning
I said I went outside last night
'cause of a noise I heard?
Yeah, Captain Park said he heard it too.
Yeah. And I really didn't think
it was strange then.
Only now, looking back at it,
when I saw him,
he was holding something in his hand.
What?
A screwdriver.
[Woo-seok] Who's there?
-[Captain] Ah. Woo-seok!
-[eerie music]
It's just Captain Park!
Screwdriver?
Mmm-hmm.
I know it was dark and all,
but I'm sure he was holding a screwdriver.
That's just a little bit weird, isn't it?
Why would he have something like that
in his hand?
Maybe he was working on the boat.
No, but he said he was in bed
when he heard the strange noise.
What if he wanted a weapon
to defend himself
'cause he felt like something was off?
Well, I guess…
-Uh, it still seems weird for--
-Woo-seok.
You think Captain Park
had something to do with this.
That is what you're saying, isn't it?
Listen, I can always trust my gut,
and it's telling me that there's
something fishy going on with the Captain.
This is the man who saved my life.
Who's spent years
trying to help me track down this island.
And even now, that's what he's doing.
I know that he is.
And look, you know, I'm not saying
he actually did anything
to the drone pilot for sure.
It's only that my gut--
Last night you were with the drone pilot.
You were drinking with him, weren't you?
[hesitating] Oh.
Yeah, but not a lot, though.
It was just a few.
[chuckles awkwardly]
We're setting out pretty early.
You should go get some sleep.
Oh.
Sure, okay.
And no more alcohol on the boat.
Starting tomorrow.
Okay.
[eerie music]
[softly] You motherfucker.
They died while you sat around.
[warped classical music playing
on speakers]
[eerie music]
-[alarm buzzing]
-[woman on PA] Your attention, please.
The fourth game will begin momentarily.
Please follow the staff's instructions
and swiftly make your way
towards the game hall.
["The Blue Danube" playing on speakers]
[Masked Officer] Sir.
The VIPs have arrived.
[music intensifies]
[woman on PA]
Players, what you see before you here
is the fate of those
who refused to accept the results
of our free and democratic voting process
by attempting to forcibly put an end
to the games through violent means.
Let us be clear.
We will not tolerate
any further irrational behavior,
-or attempts to violate the fair, just…
-[Dae-ho coughs]
…and clearly outlined rules
of these games.
Such actions will be punished
in accordance with our strict regulations.
We would like to thank you all
for your understanding and cooperation.
[eerie music]
[woman on PA]
Players, welcome to the fourth game.
For this game,
you will be divided into two teams.
Before we can begin,
all players must first receive
their team assignments.
Please step forward one at a time
and draw a ball
from the machine in front of you.
Major internal organs look good.
I was able to stitch him up.
-But?
-He needs a transfusion to live.
And we don't have any blood here.
Use mine then.
What's your type?
Type O.
That should work, right?
-[mechanical clicking]
-[mysterious music]
[mechanical clicking]
Oh, it's all right.
They haven't even said what we're playing.
-[mechanical clicking]
-[ball clattering]
[dark music]
Try anything, and you're dead.
[masked manager]
The game you'll be playing today
is Hide-and-seek.
[players] Hide-and-seek?
[masked manager] Players on the Blue Team
must either find the exit
and escape within 30 minutes,
or stay hidden to avoid being caught
by members of the Red Team
before the game ends.
Then what do we do?
Is it like the kids' version?
Do we just have to find them
and then they're out?
Players on the Red Team
must find the members of the Blue Team
hiding throughout the arena
and kill them within 30 minutes.
-[players gasp, murmur]
-[dark music]
[woman] We have to kill them?
-You did say "kill," right?
-[masked manager] That is correct.
Each player on the Red Team must find
and kill a player on the Blue Team.
If you fail to kill at least one,
you will be eliminated.
So all those people,
they're going to try to kill us?
That is correct.
[players murmuring]
[Yong-sik and Geum-ja breathing shakily]
What's this?
[masked manager]
The item you've been given is a key
that can be used
to unlock doors in the arena.
Using these keys, you will be able
to access new areas during the game.
However, once a door has been opened,
it cannot be locked again.
Whoa, hold on. So those guys
can either hide and wait it out,
or they use their keys to escape?
Sounds like an unfair advantage to me.
-What the fuck!
-Shut the hell up!
It's not just that. You're saying that
we each gotta kill one, right?
And without any tools?
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense at all.
I don't suppose any of them
will just stand there and ask us to do it.
You guys really expect us to do it
with our bare hands?
[masked manager] These points are valid,
and we completely understand
your concerns.
That's why we've gone ahead and prepared
a small gift for the Red Team as well.
Please open your boxes
and inspect their contents.
Thank you, sir.
-[players murmuring]
-[woman 1] Is that a knife?
Whoa, nice.
[woman 2] They've got knives now.
[man 1] What did we get?
-[Nam-gyu] Oh.
-[man 1] What are we to do against knives?
[Nam-gyu exclaims in awe]
[masked manager] You can use these knives
to attack the players on the Blue Team.
But please note, members of the Red Team
are not allowed to attack each other.
Well, shouldn't you at least give us
a shield or something?
They got knives after all.
What are we supposed to do,
run around without any defense?
He's right.
-You need to give us something too.
-I agree.
Look, dude, all we got were these keys.
That's not very fair, is it?
Yeah, he's right.
Those keys open doors, remember?
You people can actually get outta here.
-That's right.
-Or you can just find somewhere to hide.
-You got it easy, man!
-[man 1] Totally!
[man 2] Yeah, it's like a cake walk
for you guys.
Hey, Gramps.
You're good at that kind of thing,
aren't you?
Hiding, like a little rat.
[masked manager]
Before we begin today's game,
we would like to first give you
an opportunity to change your fate.
If any of you are not satisfied
with your currently assigned role,
you may instead choose to switch sides
with someone from the opposing team
before the game begins.
-[man 1] What? Change teams?
-[man 2] What? We can switch sides?
[masked manager] That is correct.
-As long as both parties agree…
-[prays indistinctly]
…you may trade your vests and items
with another player.
However, once the game begins,
removing your own vest,
or attempting to switch vests
with any player,
is strictly prohibited.
So please consider carefully
before making your decision.
[man 3] Well, I don't know
which team's got it worse.
-The key's not bad.
-[breath trembling]
All right, guys.
Say hi to the new drone pilot.
[drone operator] Nice to meet you all.
He was hard to find,
so make sure he feels welcome.
[mercenaries] Yes, sir.
[drone operator] Thanks.
-Right then. First things first.
-[eerie music]
-[phone buzzing]
-Go and grab a life jacket.
Don't want any more accidents.
-You heard what happened.
-[drone operator] Ah, yeah.
We're about to head out. Where are you?
[Woo-seok] Detective, you guys go ahead.
I'm not coming.
What do you mean, you're not?
[Woo-seok]
There's just something I gotta look into.
Is this about what you said last night?
I know it sounds weird,
but my gut tends to be right.
I'll be in touch if I find anything.
Until I do, be careful around the Captain.
[Jun-ho] Woo-seok--
[Captain] All right, boys,
it's time to shove off!
-Ready?
-Yeah, all set.
All right, dude, will you explain
what the hell's going on now?
What are you doing here,
and why'd you call me up so early?
I got work now.
I like to sleep in on my days off.
Your old boss is dead.
What? What do you mean, he's dead?
What happened to him?
It's a bit of a long story.
-[sighs]
-I don't…
Why the hell didn't you call me?
Why didn't I know? Huh?
Yeah, I left the crew to go straight,
but still. It's the boss--
No, it's not like that, okay? I…
You know Rock, Paper, Scissors, Minus One?
Yeah, of course.
Okay. Well, so the boss and I
were playing it like this, and…
And he needed to take back one hand.
Anyway…
Uh, let's go get hangover soup
and head out, okay?
Hey, come on, man, what happened then?
Finish the story.
Just start the car.
I'll fill you in on the way.
-I swear, you're being weird, dude.
-[engine starts]
How does someone die playing
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Minus One, huh?
Not a single one of you
will leave here alive,
-not while you walk alone.
-[woman gasps] Then what do we do?
And so instead,
it is I, Seon-nyeo, Shaman of the Sea,
who will guide your way
to find the path of life.
[players praying indistinctly]
I see everything inside this place.
And I can see the way ahead,
all from here.
[players praying indistinctly]
[Seon-nyeo] It is not with my eyes I see!
The gods of heaven and earth themselves
have taken my hand.
They're guiding us with their light!
Those who choose to follow me
-shall prolong their lives…
-[Nam-gyu] Hey, Min-su.
[Seon-nyeo] And those who stand in my way
-You ever killed anyone?
-[Seon-nyeo] …will fall dead!
[Nam-gyu] Look, there's not much time.
If you can't do this,
you might as well switch teams right now.
I know you're pretty good at hiding.
Ah, Min-su.
I was looking everywhere for you
last night, but
I couldn't find you.
Where'd you run off to?
Dude, you were scared of me, weren't you?
Nice work.
-[withdraws hand]
-You were smart to hide.
And that bitch, dude,
thought she was Wonder Woman.
She always treated me like I was nothing.
What a fucking cunt!
-She got what she…
-[breath shakes]
-[chuckles softly]
-[dark music]
Did you see it?
Oh, you little bastard,
you fucking saw it.
And you just hid there like a baby
and watched her die.
You didn't do anything.
And that bitch
really had a soft spot for you.
Aww!
Poor Min-su.
I just love that look in your eye.
Keep that going
once you get in there, bro.
Then you just gotta take them out.
[knife clatters]
That fucking son of a bitch Thanos
is dead.
And same with our whole crew.
It's just you and me now.
Think how lonely I'll be
if I lose you too.
[breathes heavily]
So I need you to be a man
this time, Min-su. Hmm?
[picks up knife]
[imitating Thanos]
You can do it, my bro, Min-su!
Min-su!
See you soon, Min-su! [laughs]
[Myung-gi] Jun-hee, switch with me.
You take the key.
It's our only way out of this.
Leave me alone.
I don't need your charity.
What do you mean, leave you alone?
I know that you won't be able
to hurt anyone with that thing.
You don't know anything about me.
Maybe not, but I do know this…
You're not a murderer.
Here, hand it over.
I'll go in and find someone to take out.
Then I'll come find you.
I'll do what it takes.
For you and our kid.
It's that easy for you to kill someone?
Yes.
I'd do anything for you and the reward,
even if it meant killing everyone.
And I'd do anything to keep my baby safe.
Then…
kill me in there.
I'll come find you once the game starts.
Then you stab me and get out, okay?
You'll both get to live then.
[Yong-sik] Mom,
give me the knife.
Oh, no, I… I can find another player
on your team to switch with.
-That way we can stay together and keep--
-Mom, please.
You know how bad your knees are.
As soon as we're in the game room,
then those assholes with their knives
will be on us like a pack of wolves.
If you and I try to stick together
the whole time,
they're gonna hunt us down.
[Geum-ja hesitates, sighs]
Oh, no. I know my son.
Even if you had one of these,
you couldn't kill anyone.
Even when you were a kid,
you'd get in those fights
in the neighborhood,
you'd get so beat up
'cause you'd just stand there.
You've never even thrown a punch,
Yong-sik, let alone killed anyone.
You're no different.
Could you chase someone down
and kill them with that?
Dad beat you all the time,
but you never fought back or anything.
I'll do it.
I…
I will try.
-[both breathe shakily]
-[tense music]
-Thank you.
-[Yeong-sam] Sweet!
Yeah. [chuckles]
Ah, shit.
Much appreciated! [laughs]
I, uh… I was just wondering
if, um, you'd consider switching.
[music intensifies]
[Dae-ho] Just hear me out, please.
Look, if you switch with me,
I can stay right with you,
and make sure you're safe. Huh?
You'd still need to kill another player.
Jesus! Just…
Look. Just… just listen.
I'll handle that, don't worry.
I'll still keep you safe, I swear.
-[gasps]
-Trust me.
Listen, I won't let you down.
Please.
Hey.
[frustrated sigh]
[breath trembling]
[mumbling] You motherfucking fuck.
You fucking piece of shit, motherfucker.
What? What's your deal, huh?
Why do you keep on staring at me?
What?
You think that it's my fault
we're still here?
That it's all because of what I did?
We couldn't have won, Gi-hun.
And it was stupid to ever think we could.
-God damn it!
-[box thuds]
Will you quit looking at me like that?!
This is not my fault!
Listen, we should've gone after
those bastards who hit the "O" button,
then we would've had a chance.
We could've won the fight.
We could've won the vote!
This is your fault.
You and your ridiculous plan,
that's why everybody else is dead.
This is all your fault!
You're the one who got them all killed!
[breathing heavily]
[solemn music]
[woman on PA] Attention.
The game will begin momentarily.
All players on the Blue Team,
please get ready.
You'll be entering the arena first.
Let me repeat the announcement.
The game will begin momentarily.
[Captain] What happened to Woo-seok?
He's not coming?
He called me
just before we left the docks.
Said he had a family emergency.
All of a sudden?
-[scoffs] Guess so.
-Maybe he got scared and bolted.
You know, that's the thing,
guys like him
who always act so tough and talk so loud,
they're a bunch of cowards in the end.
I see it as a good thing.
All he ever did
was drown himself in booze, anyway.
[solemn music]
Mom, please, find a good spot to hide.
I'll just get it over with,
and come find you.
All right?
I'll stay with you and I'll keep you safe.
Yong-sik, I'll be okay.
I mean, think how often your dad
threatened to kill me when he was drunk.
In the end,
which one of your parents died first?
Dad did.
So you really think I'm gonna die here?
[whispering] Besides,
I have my secret weapon.
And I'll use it if I have to.
So don't worry, I'll be just fine.
You focus on making it through.
Whatever it takes,
whatever you need to do,
so we can leave this place together. Huh?
[chuckles]
Swear on your life.
I swear I'll find you.
-[eerie music]
-[players gasp, murmur]
[man] Where do we go?
-[door thuds]
-[players gasp]
-[timer beeps]
-[woman on PA] You now have two minutes.
I repeat, two minutes
until the Red Team enters the arena.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Everyone.
We should all spread out.
And don't just try to hide.
We need to look for the exit.
Once someone finds a way out of here,
they should shout it out.
So that way, we can all come to them.
Good. Yeah, that's a good plan.
Yeah, if we just work together,
then we can all get out of here
in one piece.
[child's voice on PA]
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play ♪
-♪ Don't let your hair give you away ♪
-[players clamoring]
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your clothes give you away ♪
Don't let your toe give you away ♪
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your hair give you away ♪
Wanna work together?
What?
-[Nam-gyu chuckles softly]
-[tense music]
Think they'll just let us kill them?
Come on now, use your head. 'Course not.
They'll come at us
with everything they have,
which means,
if we work as a team in there,
we're gonna have the advantage.
♪ Don't let your hair give you away ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your clothes give you away ♪
Are you okay?
[Hyun-ju] Ms. Geum-ja, Jun-hee.
♪ Don't let your toe give you away ♪
We'll go together.
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your hair give you away ♪
-Watch your step.
-[Geum-ja] Uh-huh.
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your clothes… ♪
Fuck, I'm not asking for,
like, a relationship or anything.
Just a one-night stand.
♪ Don't let your clothes give you away ♪
When you took out Thanos like that,
that was just… [clears throat]
…fucking amazing.
-♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play ♪
-[timer beeps]
[woman on PA]
Red Team, please enter the arena.
So we a team?
Hmm?
[imitating Thanos] Let's get it!
[music intensifies]
It's all your fault.
[intense music]